mrcheapstuff.com 2009-03-27

# Privacy Policy : Mr. Cheap Stuff

[](http://feeds.feedburner.com/MrCheapStuff) If you're new here you may want to join the 10,000+ smart shoppers that that subscribe to my [RSS feed](http://feeds.feedburner.com/MrCheapStuff) or Free Newsletter. Thanks for visiting! - Dean aka Mr. Cheap Stuff

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:** This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the MrCheapStuff.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information (etc.) On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name Address Phone Number (etc.)

**The Way We Use Information:** We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?** We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein.

**How To Contact Us** Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies send us an email at info@mrcheapstuff.com

    At MrCheapStuff.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit MrCheapStuff.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

    Log Files  
    As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

    Cookies and Web Beacons  
    We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

    We also use third party advertisements on MrCheapStuff.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

    You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Related Coupons:
